<resources>
    <string name="app_name">2048</string>

    <string name="version">v1.0</string>
    <string name="author">Ban Rossyn</string>

    <!--google play service project id-->
    <string name="Googleplay_games_App_ID">523708674078</string>

    <!--    admobe-->
    <string name="App_ID">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544~3347511713</string>
    <string name="BannerAd">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/6300978111</string>
    <string name="InterstitialAd">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/1033173712</string>

    <!--    Playstore account link-->
    <string name="moregamesurl">https://play.google.com/store/apps/dev?id=5306067645342206751</string>

    <string name="game_over_title">Game Over</string>
    <string name="mode_classic">Classic</string>
    <string name="mode_blocks">Blocks</string>
    <string name="mode_shuffle">Shuffle</string>
    <string name="mode_exp_classic">The good old classic 2048</string>
    <string name="mode_exp_blocks">Random blocks will spawn in your board</string>
    <string name="mode_exp_shuffle">"Your board knows how to Shuffle!! "</string>
    <string name="exponent_exp_2">Try to get the \n2048 Tile!</string>
    <string name="exponent_exp_3">Try to get the \n177,147 Tile!</string>
    <string name="exponent_exp_4">Try to get the \n4,194,304 Tile!</string>
    <string name="exponent_exp_5">Try to get the \n48,828,125 Tile!</string>
    <string name="start">Start!</string>
    <string name="end_tutorial">End Tutorial</string>
    <string name="shuffle">Shuffle!</string>
    <string name="new_game">New Game</string>
    <string name="Score_board">Score Board</string>
    <string name="choose_game_mode">Choose Game Mode</string>
    <string name="choose_board_size">Choose Board Size</string>
    <string name="square">Square</string>
    <string name="rectangle">Rectangle</string>
    <string name="choose_exponent">Choose Exponent</string>
    <string name="on">On</string>
    <string name="off">Off</string>
    <string name="play">Play!</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="music">Music</string>
    <string name="sound">Sound</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="your_score">your score</string>
    <string name="play_again">Play Again</string>
    <string name="how_to_play">How to Play</string>
    <string name="best_score">Best :</string>
    <string name="winner">Winner!!!</string>
    <string name="new_score">New Score!!!</string>

    <string name="tutorial_first_line">How to play:\nSwipe Up , Down , left , right to Move the Tiles Across the Board</string>
    <string name="tutorial_second_line">GOOD!! \nTwo Identical Tiles will Merge when they Collide, Try to Merge the Tiles</string>
    <string name="tutorial_third_line">Perfect!!\nContinue to Merge the Tiles and Try to get a Higher Score!</string>
    <string name="textfrist">Join the numbers and reach the 2048 tile! Supports small (3x3),(3x4),(3x5),
        classic (4x4),(4x5) large (5x5),(5x6), and Huge (6x6),board sizes. Be ready for a new challenge!</string>
    <string name="textsecond">Super 2048 Plus puzzle Keep playing for high score after
        collected 2048 tile Game is automatically saved and continue to play later.
        Beautiful, simple and classic design.</string>
    <string name="textthird">Block Tiles in Game. click and swipe sound with Background music</string>
    <string name="textforth">High score and leaderboard for different board sizes.
        Completely native implementation. Play on any part of the screen.
        Classic game play with silky-smooth movements Swipe to move Undo button to reverse a swipe Detailed statistics
        including best scores Always free with no purchase required Official version of the original puzzle game</string>
    <string name="textfive">HOW TO PLAY: Swipe (up, down, left or right) to move the tiles.
        When two tiles with the same number touch, they merge into one. When a 2048 tile is created,
        the player wins! 8 .. 16 .. 128 .. 1024 .. 2048.
       </string>
    <string name="textsix"> Short Descripation: 2048 is played on a plain 4×4 grid,
        consisting of numbered tiles that slide when a player moves them using the four arrow keys. On each turn,
        a new tile randomly appears on an empty spot on the board with a value of 2 or 4.
        The tiles slide as far as possible in the chosen direction until they are stopped by another tile or the edge of the grid.
        If two tiles of the same number collide while moving, they will merge into one tile with the total value of the two tiles colliding.
        The resulting tile cannot merge with any other tile in the same move again. High scoring tiles emit a soft glow;
        The highest possible tile is 131,072. If a move causes three consecutive tiles of the same value to move simultaneously,
        only the two tiles that are farthest in the direction of motion will combine.
        If all four spaces in a row or column are filled with tiles of the same value, a move parallel to that row/column will add the first two and
        the last two. A scoreboard in the top right keeps track of the user\'s score. The user\'s score starts at zero,
        and increases by the value of the new tile each time two tiles meet. The game is won when a tile with the value 2048
        appears on the board. Players can go beyond this and reach higher scores. When the player has no legal moves
        (there are no spaces and no adjacent tiles with the same value), the game ends.
       </string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="games">SIGN IN</string>
    <string name="more_games">more games</string>
    <string name="signin_other_error">Signin Error</string>

</resources>